Ah, hello.
あ、こんにちは
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Mika-san.
みかさん
Ah, yes, that's right.
あ、 はい、そうです
Sorry, thank you in advance.
すいません、よろしくお願いします
It's raining.
雨ですね
It's amazing, the rain.
すごいですね、雨が
It's raining.
雨ですね
Actually, I was hoping we could talk while walking.
ちょっと本当は、歩きながらおしゃべりできたらなと思ってた
But.
んです けど
Well, it's raining.
まあ、雨なんで
yes.
はい
Shall we go to a cafe?
カフェ行きましょうか
I'm going.
行きます
Yes, thank you very much.
はい、よろしくお願いします
please.
お願いします
Unfortunately it was raining today.
今日、あいにくでしたね、雨で
No, really.
いや、本当に
It's surprisingly sunny and warm.
意外と晴れ温度だったりするんですけど
I am there too.
自分もいますね
I use a lot of sunscreen.
日焼け止めめっちゃ出てます
Was there someone like this?
こういう人いた?
Ah, there you are.
あ、いますね
And here.
で、ここ
Look for someone.
誰かを探して
I don't go that far, but sometimes the sun stings.
そこまではやらないんですけど、日が刺さったりとか
The sun will be refreshing everywhere.
どこでも日がさっぱししくなりますよ
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなんですか?
No, don't you feel bad?
いや、気持ち悪くないですか?
It's like direct sunlight.
なんか、直射日光が
I want a tan.
日 焼 けが欲しいな
It might be important.
大事かもしれないです
I don't want to bake it.
焼きたくないとかしなくて
Probably because it's hot.
熱いからでしょうね
Yes, it's hot.
そう、熱いから
Is it me?
私ですか?
Yes, not anymore.
はい、もうじゃないです
No, I've never had one.
いや、持ってたことないですよ
it is?
それは?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだ
No, that's right.
いや、そうですね
いや、そう
Who are you?
誰ですか?
Such a wonderful person.
こんな素敵な方
Was he such a wonderful person?
こんな素敵な方だったの?
I was at the top.
私、上の方だったんですよ
Above?
上で?
yes.
はい
I was surprised.
びっくりしましたね
There are beautiful people.
綺麗な人いる
No, thank you very much.
いや、ありがとうございます
Thank you.
ありがとさんだった
I was surprised.
びっくりしました
thank you.
ありがと
Not in front of me.
目の前にいない
Yes, it is.
はい、ですよ
Why is that?
それはなんで?
picture?
え?
There's no one to tell me.
言ってきてくれる人いないです
Are you the summer type?
夏のタイプですか?
It's a summer type.
夏タイプです
No, you can't go.
いや、行けないでしょ
It's just not possible.
ちょっとだって、無理だなって
I can't really go on my own.
なんか自分からグイグイ行けない
Are you quite sensitive?
結構おしに弱いですか?
Ah, but I'm weak.
あ、でもおしに弱いです
Are you sensitive to butts?
おしに弱いですか?
It's better to be weak in the butt.
おしに弱い方がいいですよ
I can't go there normally, like this.
普通行けないですよ、この感じの
This finished person.
この出来上がった人
is that so?
そうですか?
Aren't you a confident man?
自信がある男性じゃないですか?
There is also Mercan.
メルカンもあるんですけどね
No, that's impossible.
いや、無理ですね
If it were me, I wouldn't be able to do it.
僕だったら無理です
I like cute people.
可愛い感じの人が好きで
She's quite the sexual type.
結 構、性がめっちゃ出たタイプで
When it comes to cute, there are quite a lot of things.
可愛いって言うと、結構いろいろあるんですよ
I don't like bad guys though.
ダメなやつは嫌なんですけど
I also like people who are born cute.
可愛いって、生まれる人も好きで
There's something called sweet love.
甘え恋ってやつが
What kind of things do you have?
どういうのがありますか?
for example?
例えば?
Being pampered is such a mess
甘えられるって、めちゃくちゃ
I like it.
好 きです
I can't be spoiled.
甘えてきません
You've been spoiled.
甘えてきましたね
I can't be spoiled.
甘えられないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
Looks like it's coming.
寄ってくるみたいな
It's like they're coming.
寄 ってくるみたいな
Looks like he'll follow me.
ついてくれるみたいな
I'm glad you came.
来てくれるのが嬉しいですね
I like it earlier in the week.
週上がいいんです
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくないですか?
On the week above.
週上で
That's the gap,
それがギャップで、
The more people are separated.
人 が離れてるほど
That's how many people there are.
そういうぐらいの人が
that's right.
そうです
How many people?
何個目ぐらいの人?
At the top,
一番上で、
I can get around 47 or 48.
47、 48ぐらいはいけます
father?
お父さん?
I'm sure though.
確かになりますけど
younger than
よりは若い
that's right.
そうです
I can't help it.
しょうがない
I want to pull it out now.
今、引っ張って行きたい
I want you to pull me out, but I like the gap.
引っ張って欲しいんですけど、 ギャップが好きで、
Even though I'm the one above you, when it comes to the two of you,
上の人なのに、 じゃあ、いざ2人になったら、
That's amazing.
すごいな
I feel spoiled.
甘えが来たり
I become a bit of a tsundere.
ちょっとツンデレになるんですけど
It's good because it's just two people.
2人だからいいっすね
that's right.
そうです
If I saw it, I wouldn't want to see it.
僕が見たら見てらんないですよね
Outside on top, 2 people 2 people.
上に外、2人2人
like.
好き
Summer is a shame.
夏は惜しい
They're not very useful together.
一緒にあんまり役に立たないですね
Even if I go with you, I won't be able to get a job anymore.
一緒に行っても、 もう仕事が取らないですね
I have eyes.
目があるんですけど
Dog type.
犬系
It's dog-like.
犬系ですね
Hira.
ひら
It's quite painful.
なかなか痛いですし
appear before your eyes.
目の前に現れる
It's like, Wow.
なんか、 わー、みたいな
together
一緒
Well, let's just wait, or say anything is fine as long as it's cool.
に 待とうというか、 かっこよく言えば何でもいいって言うしか
do not have.
ない
Isn't it good?
いい んじゃない?
Do you have any plans?
皆さんは何かご予定とかあります?
I'm staying at a nearby hotel.
近くのホテルに泊まってるんですけど、
If you'd like, change the location, um, your room.
よかったら場所変えて、 あの、部屋とか
Well, it's my first time meeting you, but...
まあ、初対面なんであれなんですけど、
If there is no resistance, I will not predict it.
もし抵抗がなければ、 ご予想しません
I'd love to.
是非
OK?
大丈夫 ですか?
Yes, it's okay.
はい、大丈夫です
Well then, thank you very much.
じゃあ、 よろしくお願いします
Well then, let's move.
じゃあ、移動しましょうか
Can I sit there?
そこ座っていいですか?
I made some very frightening suggestions,
結構、恐ろ恐ろ提案したんですけど、
They usually come.
普通に来てくれるんですよね
yes.
はい
It's like shaa.
しゃーみたいな
Okay.
よっしゃー
I'm not saying that, but that's what I'm talking about right now.
よ っしゃーじゃないですけど、 今のはあれですけど、
I really mean it, but...
本心ですけど、 です けど、ちょっと、
I didn't think he would come.
来 てくれると思わなかった
No, I'm nervous, but
いや、 緊 張しますが、
No, it's true.
いや、 ほんとですよ
It's true.
ほんとですよ
That's quite a bit, but in hotels etc.
結構あれですけど、 ホテルとかに、
Do you feel like not much these days?
最近はあんまりないって感じですか?
No.
ないです
That's terrible.
やばいですね
Sorry, that's something.
それは、 すみません、なんか
For a while, I won't be able to say anything but dangerous things.
ちょっと、しばらくやばいしか言えなくなっちゃうわけですね
difference
さ
I didn't realize it, but my legs...
っ き気づかなかったですけど、 足が、
It's out.
出てますね
My legs are sticking out, yes.
足が出てます、はい
It's out.
出 てます
I didn't notice it earlier, but it's here.
さっき気づかなかったですけど、 出てます
It was out.
出てましたね
Since when did you come out?
いつから出てました?
It's out all the time.
ずっと出てますよ
Is it true?
ほんとですか?
I only saw the face, so I don't know.
ちょっと顔しか見てなくて、わかんない
It's out all the time.
ずっと出てます
It was out.
出てましたね
Wind, are you barefoot?
風、 生足ですか?
Bare legs.
生足です
It was cold.
寒かったです
Are you cold?
冷えました?
That's pretty much it. I was just outside a little while ago.
結構あれですか、こう、 さっきはちょっと外だったんで、
I couldn't really listen to it, but
あんまり聞けなかったんですけど、
This kind of thing, so-called, I met on the internet,
こういうこう、いわゆる、 ネットでしにあって、
Let's meet up,
待ち合わせして、
Does it happen sometimes?
た まにあります?
sometimes.
たまに
It's cute.
かわいいですね
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine
結構こう、 結構、
I've heard that you go into quite a bit of detail,
結 構踏み込んだこと聞きますけど、
Do you have a sex friend?
セフレとかはいます?
Are you there?
います?
There you are.
いますね
I can only feel like I'm there.
いるのかいって感じしかない
There is.
いるんですね
Then, surprisingly, unexpectedly, various things,
じゃあ意外と、 意外と、 いろいろ、
Are you an older sister?
お姉さん系ですか?
Is that so?
そうなんですかね
Do you feel like you don't know then?
それならわからないって感じですか?
Yes, just a moment.
はい、ちょっと
Do you feel like you don't even understand?
自分でもわかりませんって感じですか?
Because I don't understand.
わかりませんから
On the contrary, I don't get many approaches from serious people.
そういう、 逆に真剣な人から、 アプローチがあんま来ないか
I can't do it.
もし れない
Are there quite a lot of men who are attracted to women?
女性に惹かれてくる男だけ結構多いんですか?
Well, well, all kinds of things.
まあまあまあ、 いろんなね
various.
いろんな
After all, I was drawn to this place,
やっぱ、 ここにこう、 引っ付けられるとか、
I'll stop by and do it, after all,
寄ってやっちゃいますし、 やっぱこう、
My legs are sticking out too.
足もこんだけ出てる
I'm sure you're curious.
や っぱ気になっちゃいますよね
I'm curious.
気になっちゃいます
Do you feel like this is keeping you at bay?
これで寄せ付けてるって感じですか?
That's not true.
違いますよ
I can't help but think about this.
寄せ付けられますけど、これ
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
It's cold.
冷えてますよ
Was it cold?
寒かったですか?
Aren't your hands warm?
手あったかくないですか?
this.
これ
It's really warm.
めっちゃあったかいです
It's really warm, isn't it?
めっちゃあったかいですよね
It's really warm.
めっちゃあったかいですよ
めっちゃあったかいです
It was really hot.
め っちゃ あ った か い ですよ
this.
これ
It was so warm.
めっちゃあったかくて
Oh, it's cold.
あ、冷えてます
Warm.
あったかい
It's just warm.
普通にあったかいっていう
Eh, isn't it quite warm here?
え、こっち結構あったかくないですか?
This one.
こっちの
Is it warm?
あったかいですか?
Ah, but it might still be cold.
あ、でもまだ冷えてるかも
Please let me know if it doesn't work.
ダメだったら言ってくださいね
I keep coming to the conclusion that it's not okay.
ダメじゃないって判断をどんどんしちゃうんで
It's really beautiful, isn't it?
めっちゃ綺麗ですよね
What's wrong?
どうかしましたか?
There's nothing, right?
何もないですよね
Nothing, right?
何 もないですよね
What's wrong?
どうかしましたか?
There's nothing, right?
何もないですよね
Nothing?
何もないです?
What's wrong?
どうかしましたか?
I'm just looking at your face all the time.
僕ずっと顔見てるだけなんで
I feel embarrassed, I guess.
照れますね、なんかね
Did something happen?
何かありました?
I feel kind of embarrassed.
なんか照れちゃいます
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That's right, a little after all.
ですよね、ちょっとやっぱ
It would be embarrassing if there were two people in the room.
部屋に2人だと照れますね
Is that enough to make you feel embarrassed?
それだけで照れます?
I'm embarrassed.
照れます
Your hair is beautiful.
髪の毛綺麗ですね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Can I touch your hair?
触っていいですか、髪の毛?
That's fine.
いいですよ
It's hair
髪の毛よ
Can you touch me?
く 触られますか?
No, I don't touch it much.
いや、あまり触られないです
That's right.
ですよね
Can't you touch me like this?
あんまこうやって触られないですか?
It's my first time.
初めてです
Nothing at all, for now.
全然何もないですよね、今のところ
Nothing.
何もないです
It looks like it's visible.
見えそうで見えるんですよね
yes.
そう
I was curious and did it on my own.
気になっちゃって、勝手に
I got curious.
気 になっちゃって
I wonder what's going on.
僕、どうなっているのかなって
Are you curious?
気になりますよね?
I'm curious.
気になるんですよ
I have a lot of heart.
心が結構あって
He'll understand.
わかってくれますよ
I can understand why you're concerned.
気になっちゃうのわかります
That's right.
そうなんですよ
I'm really curious.
めっちゃ気になっちゃう
I'm a little concerned.
ちょっと気になっちゃう
It's my first time meeting someone, so there's probably a lot of things I don't know.
初めてお会いする方なんで、いろいろ知らないとかあるじゃない
Is it?
ですか
There are so many things I don't know.
知 らないことだらけですもんね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
You get to know it whether you take the time or not.
時間かけたりかけなかったりして知っていくじゃないですか
yes.
はい
So a little bit
なのでちょっと
...
I might be wrong today...maybe it's too early.
今日は 間違い...早いかもしれないですね
yes,
はい、
Good... looking good.
いい...いい格好ですね
Are you looking good?
いい格好ですか?
Oh no.
やば
It looks a little erotic.
ちょっとエロい格好ですね
Just a little bit more...ah...
これちょっともうちょい...あ、
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
this.
これ
Here is a two-shot of your face.
ここと、お顔のツーショットですけど
Are you okay.
大丈夫
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
That's right.
そうですよ
If there were two people...
2人だったら...
that's right.
そうです
It's okay if there are two people.
2人だったら大丈夫
As for earlier...if there was a third party...
さっきの...第三者がいたら...
That's a bit true, though.
ちょっとさすがにあれなんですけど
I don't understand.
分かんないですね
Don't you understand?
分かんないですか?
I don't understand.
分かんないですね
Can I take a closer look?
もうちょい近くで見てもいいですか?
Are you looking at it up close?
近くで見るんですか?
yes.
はい
That's fine.
いいですよ
May I?
いいですか?
I don't see it outside, of course.
外では見ないですよ、もちろん
It's okay if it's just the two of us.
2人きりだったら大丈夫
I'll take a closer look outside.
外では近くで見ます
Please come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち来てください
what?
何?
It also has legs.
足もついて
It's very close, isn't it?
めちゃくちゃ近いじゃないですか?
Oh, wait... can't you see?
あ、ちょっと...見えない?
You can't see this.
これは見えないですよね
Tsk.
ちっか
I don't know if I can smell it.
匂いは分かられるような分からない
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
What do you have?
何があるんですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
I can't see it.
見えてないですよ
You can't see it, but it's very close, isn't it?
見えてないけどめちゃくちゃ近いじゃないですか?
Yes, it's close.
ちょっとはい、近いんですよ
I can't see it.
見えないんです
I can't see it, but my nose...
見えないけど鼻...
I have no choice but to rely on the smell.
匂い頼りにするしかなくて
I'm not kidding.
ふざけてないです
Seriously.
真面目に
Are you serious?
真面目にやってるんですか?
I'm doing this seriously.
真面目にやってます
You can't see it.
見えないですよね
I can't see it.
見えないんで
yes.
はい
I can't see it.
見えないんで
That's all...
これだけ...
Can you take your clothes off?
脱いだりするってことできます?
Is this it?
これですか?
yes.
はい
You can take it off.
脱げます
I'll take it off.
脱ぎます
You can't see it.
見えないんだね
Please take off your clothes for a while.
ちょっと脱いでもらって
It's better if you can see it.
見えた方がいいですもんね
I just want to take a look.
ちょっと見たいんで
I'll take it off.
脱ぎますね
脱ぎます
yes.
はい
amazing.
すごい
Did you take it off?
脱ぎました?
I took it off.
脱ぎました
It may not be visible.
見えないかもしれない
I can't see it.
見えないですね
please show me.
見せてください
Are you going to show it?
見せるんですか?
yes.
はい
I can't see it yet.
まだ見えてない
まだ見えてないです
I can't see it yet.
まだ見えてない
You can see it, right?
見えてるじゃないですか?
I can't see it.
見えてないです
You can't see it unless you lift your legs.
足あげないと見えないです
Oh, I can't see it.
あ、見えてないです
I can't see it.
見えてないです
見えてないんですよ
Can't you see it?
見えてないんですか?
I can't see it.
見えてないです
見えてないですね
It might be easier to see if you raise your legs.
足を上げてもらった方が見えやすいかもしれない
You can definitely see it, right?
絶対見えてるじゃないですか
I can't see it well.
よくは見えてないです
I could see it just now, but the angle...
今ちょっと見えたんですけど、 角度が...
The angle...
角度が...
Isn't the angle too steep?
角度が急じゃないですか
May I have a look?
ちょっと見してもらっていいですか
The angle is steep.
角度が急ですよ
What do you mean, the angle is sudden?
どういうことですか、角度が急って
The angle is steep.
角度が急ですよ
The angle is steep...
角度が急...
I don't know.
わかんないです
I don't know, but
わかんないんですけど、
I can see it now.
今 見えてます
Did you see it?
見えました?
Now that I think about it, I can see it.
そういえば今見えてます
May I take a closer look?
近くで見ていいですか
That's fine.
いいですよ
May I.
いい ですか
If you don't have one, you might be able to see it even if you get close.
1枚なければ、寄っても見えるかもしれない
I see.
なるほど
You can't see it anymore, can you?
もうそれ見えてないじゃないですか
Can you see it?
見えてますか
You can see a nice pattern.
いい柄が見えてますよ
May I take a closer look?
近くで見ていいですか
Can you see it?
見えるんですか
Hey, already.
ねえ、もう
I can't see it.
見えてないです
Do you see that?
見えてますか、それ
You can't see it.
見えてないですよね
No, wait a minute.
いや、ちょっと待って
I'm licking it.
舐めてますね
I licked it.
舐めちゃった
I can't see it, wait.
見えないね、ちょっと
Nearby...
近くとこう...
It's a matter of taste.
味覚ですから
Someone is licking me hard.
がっつり舐めてる人が
I'm licking it without permission.
勝手に舐めてますよ
Excuse me for a moment.
ちょっと、すみません
yes.
はい
Can I take this off?
これ脱がしていいですか
Is this also?
これもですか
I thought it might get dirty.
汚れちゃうかなと思って
I see.
なるほど
That's fine.
いいですよ
Is it okay?
いいんですか
This is so amazing...
なんかすごいこう...
It was moving for a while.
ちょっと、動いてたんで
It wasn't moving, I guess.
動いてませんでした、なんか
I agree.
そうですね
It was moving a bit, so I took it off.
ちょっと動いてたんで、脱がします
It was moving.
動いてたんで
There's something so erotic in it.
こんなエロいのが入ってるんですね
It's too late though.
今更ですけど
If you hide it, it will become embarrassing.
隠すと恥ずかしいものになっちゃいますよ
Is it the other way around?
逆にですか
I'm not embarrassed.
恥ずかしくないです
It's smooth.
ツルツルっすよ
Why is it smooth?
なんでツルツル?
Has it never been born?
一度も生えてないんですか?
Isn't that true?
そんなことないですか
I'm really fidgety though.
すごいモジモジしてますけど
What is it?
なんですか
I'm not fidgeting.
モジモジしてないです
Are you fidgeting?
モジモジしてないですか
It's not that close right now, so I can see it clearly.
今 あんま近くないんでちゃんと見えてますけど
You're fidgeting, aren't you?
モジモジしてますよね
I haven't.
してないです
It's so smooth.
こんなツルツルなんですね
Is it difficult?
難しいですか?
Are you embarrassed by your lack of hair?
毛がないのが恥ずかしいですか?
Why are you so wet?
なんでこんなに濡れてるんですか?
Because I licked it?
舐めたから?
Is that too?
それもある?
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I haven't licked the inside though.
中まで舐めてないんですけど
hey.
ね
hello.
もし もし
Please don't.
しないでください
I haven't.
してないです
Haven't you?
してないですか?
I haven't.
してないです
No upper body?
上半身はしてない?
I haven't done everything.
全部してないです
I'm wearing the lower half of my body though, right?
下半身はしてるけどじゃないですか?
I haven't done everything.
全部してないです
My face is hidden.
顔が隠れてる
I won't hide this.
こっち隠さない
Both, both.
両方、両方
Both are no good.
両方ダメです
Are both bad?
両方ダメですか?
Has it gone bad?
ダメになったんですか?
now.
今更
I think the sofa is getting smaller.
ソファーが狭くなってきたと思うけど
Wouldn’t a bed be better?
ベッドのほうがよくないですか?
It's a good thing.
せっかくあるし
I agree.
そうですね
Shall we go to bed?
ベッド行きましょうか?
It's spacious.
広いんで
Please get on the bed.
ベッドの上に上がってもらって
I can see your butt though.
お尻見えてますけど
Is the bed spacious?
ベッド広いですか?
It's spacious.
広いんですね
It's wide so it's easy to spread your legs.
広いから足とか広げやすいですよね
Fair enough, sure.
まあまあ、確かに
So let's spread it out.
じゃあ広げましょうか
Shall we spread it out?
広げましょうか
Can I lean on it and spread it out?
よりかかって広げてもらっていいですか?
I'm hiding again.
また隠れてますけど
Isn't it hidden?
隠れてません?
I can't see it.
見えてません
No, you can't see it from here.
いや、こっからだと見えないんですよ
I have to get it like this.
こうしてもらわないと
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほど
Yes, like this.
はい、こう
It's getting flattened though.
ペチャペチャになってますけど
What happened?
どうしました?
What's wrong?
どうかしました?
No, I'm not doing anything.
いや、どうもしてません
Are you not doing anything?
どうもしてないですか?
I can't help it.
どうもしてないです
Ah, it's warm.
あ、温かい
It's warm.
温かいですね
Is it a little warmer at the top?
もうちょっと上も温かいですか?
Is it better to start from here?
こっちからの方がいいのかな?
Do you have it?
ありますか?
Isn't there?
ないですか?
Yes, there is.
ありますね
ありますよね
It was a little difficult to get to from the bottom.
下からだとちょっと行きづらかったね
ah.
ああ
It's nice to see the bottom.
下はいいですね、見えてて
Something like that.
なんかそうだ
yes.
はい
I'm usually alone quite a bit.
結 構お一人なんですよね、普段は
yes.
はい
Do you ever have lonely nights when you're alone?
一人の時、寂しい夜とかないですか?
There is.
ありますよ
Is it Sephrin?
セフリンのか
No, it doesn't really fit the bill.
いや、そんな的に合ってるわけじゃないです
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうですか
How many people are there?
何人かいるんですか?
picture?
え?
There are 2 people.
2人です
Who are you?
誰ですか?
I won't say it.
言わないですよ
I agree.
そうですね
But isn't that what you do when you're alone?
でもあれじゃないですか、一人でこうなんか、
Wouldn't you like to do something like this?
こにょこにょやったりしないですか?
There is.
ありますよ
Is there one?
あるんですか?
It can teach you quite a lot.
結構いろいろ教えてくれるんですね
Since it's just the two of us, I thought it would be okay to talk a little bit about various things.
2人なんでちょっといろいろ話してもいいかなと思って
Well, I won't say it for a while.
まあ、ちょっと言わないんでね
What do you use?
何使います?
I use lemma.
私はレンマ使います
It will teach you a lot.
めっちゃ教えてくれますね
Eh, what kind of chord is this? A very rugged guy who loves chords.
え、どういうコードレとか、コード好きのめっちゃごついやつ
Or something.
とか
No, that's not it.
いや、 そういうんじゃない
Kind of normal.
なんか、普通に
Eh, how old is it?
え、どんぐらいのやつ?
What kind of thing is it?
どんぐらいのやつ
Hey, just like that.
ちょ、そのまますね
Is this about it?
これぐらいですか?
About this.
これぐらい
Ah, just like that.
あ、ちょうどですね
As expected.
さすが
You are used to using it.
使い慣れてらっしゃる
What, is this what you mean?
え、こういうやつってこと?
Well, it's something like this.
え、こういうやつです
Oh, how do you use it?
お、どうやって使うんですか?
How do I use it?
どうやって使うんですか?
Hey, yes.
ちょ、はい
Well, I'll give it to you.
じゃあ、お渡しします
I'll give it to you.
お 渡ししますんで
Usually, please be patient.
普段は、 もうがっつりしてください
He can teach you anything.
なんでも教えてくれますね
Eh, where are you applying it?
え、で、どこに当ててるんですか?
Eh, where?
え、どこ?
Well, I'm getting it right now.
え、今当たってますよ
That's right.
当たってますよ
Do you guess?
当てますか?
Look.
ほら
There are two of us.
2人ですよ
Ah, yeah.
あ、うん
There are 2 people.
2人です
yes.
はい
Is that the best?
そこが一番良いですか?
yes.
はい
You guessed it.
当 ててますね
So, ah, should I guess?
じゃあ、あ、当ててるといいの?
yes.
はい
Her face is cute too.
顔も可愛いっすね
Looks embarrassing.
恥ずかしそう
How long will I have to guess it myself?
いつまで自分で当てるんですかね?
Eh, this is a bit.
え、これ、ちょっと
How long will I have to guess it myself?
いつまで自分で当てるんですか?
I'm here today.
私、今日ここにいるんで
Does it match?
あってるんですか?
Yes, I'll be there.
はい、俺があってますよ
I'm here all the time.
せっかくいるんで
What happened?
どうしました?
Leave this here, do this, do this,
ここを置いて、こうやって、こうやって、
I guess this is it.
こうかな
What's wrong?
何がダメですか?
Is it no good?
ダ メですか?
What's wrong?
何がダメですか?
何 がダメですか?
Are you guessing incorrectly?
当て方がなってないですか?
Is it different?
違 います?
Is it correct?
当たってます?
I'm right.
当たってます
Is it true?
本当ですか?
What happened?
どうしました?
If I don't know how to guess correctly, please let me know.
当て方がなってなかったら、ちゃんと言ってください
It was.
なってました
picture?
え?
Isn't it getting better?
結構良くなってきてません?
Please stop.
やめてください
What are you going to stop doing?
何をやめるの?
Is it getting much better?
結構良くなってきてるんですか?
Isn't it good?
別に良いじゃないですか?
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
No, but...
ダメですけど...
It's not bad, but it's not good.
ダメじゃないですけど、ダメです
Is it no good?
ダ メ ですか?
Something a little higher, a little lower, etc.
何か、もうちょい上とか、もうちょい下とか、
There are many reasons why I like weaker ones, right?
弱い方が好みだなとか、 何か、色々あるじゃないですか?
I think there are many things.
色々あると思うんですよ
I think there are many different kinds, depending on your preference.
色々あると思うんですよ、好みが
I think there are many different tastes.
好みが色々あると思うんですけど、
My face was hidden.
顔が隠れちゃったんですよ
I think it's embarrassing...
恥ずかしいと思います...
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
That's just my imagination.
それは気のせいです
I'm not embarrassed.
僕、恥ずかしないです
Ah, maybe it's just my imagination.
あ、気のせいですかね
Ah, it's just my imagination...
あー、気のせい...
Is it just my imagination that my hips are moving?
腰が動いてるのって、気のせいですか?
It's just my imagination.
気のせいです.
Oh?
あ、ですか?
No, is it because of?
いや、のせいですか?
It's because of this.
のせいですね
Is that so?
そう か
My hips are moving a lot.
腰めっちゃ動いてる
It's because of
のせいです
Is it because of this?
のせいですか?
yes.
はい
It's totally fine, it's a hotel.
全然大丈夫ですよ、ホテルだし
it's okay.
大丈夫です
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
It's okay, it's a hotel.
大丈夫ですよ、ホテルなんで
Oh, I'm starting to feel sensitive.
お、敏感になってきましたね、なんか
You're becoming more sensitive.
敏感になってきてますね
It's becoming more and more.
なってきてますね
yes.
はい
It's starting to happen.
なってきましたね
I'm starting to get a little sensitive, though.
ちょっと、敏感になってきてますけど、
yes.
はい
It's already tomorrow here.
明 日になってきましたね、ここは
I was moving my hips a lot.
すごい腰動いてましたけど
It's just my imagination.
気のせいです
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいですか?
yes.
はい
Is it just my imagination that it's slimy inside?
この中、ぬるぬるなのって気のせいですか?
I think it's just my imagination.
気のせいだと思います
But is that so?
ですけど、そうですかね?
yes.
はい
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいですか?
yes.
はい
I don't feel like I've licked the inside.
中まで舐めた気分ないんですよ
But something is wrong.
な のになんか
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
Is it just my imagination?
気 の せいですか?
I'm hiding my face, I can see it all the time.
顔、顔隠してるよ、こっちずっと見えてるんですよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's tough.
きついですね
May I?
いいですか?
Does this include Japanese?
これって、日本語入るのかな?
yes.
はい
He was waiting for me to come in for a while.
ちょっと入るの待っててくれたんですね
I was wondering what it was like.
ちょっとどうなのかなって思って
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
By the way, are you okay?
ちなみに大丈夫ですか?
Refers to 2 books.
指2本
I feel like it's that tough.
そんなきついかなって感じがします
That's right.
そうですよね
This is what it is, if you put it in, it won't be too tight.
これあれですよ、入れとけばきつくなくなるんで
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
I don't know.
わかんないですよ
I don't know, but I feel like that's the case.
わかんないですけど、なんかそうかなっていう
It moves a little.
ちょいちょい動くんですよ
It's just my imagination.
気のせいです
It's just a little bit of my imagination.
気のせいがちょっと多いですね
I was still moving a little.
今もちょっと動いたんですけど
yes.
はい
Does the manfish move?
マンコウ動くんですか?
I don't know.
わかんないですもんね
Don't you know?
わかんないですか?
無意識
It may be unconscious.
無意識かもしれない
It is written that the pussy moves unconsciously.
無意識にマンコウ動くって書いてある
I think it's a little more colorful.
ちょっとより色い気がする
I have no idea.
全然わかりません
I don't know.
わかんないですよ
Don't you know?
わかんないですか?
I don't know.
わか んない
It's really moving.
めっちゃ動いてますよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Even now.
今も
Look, look, look.
ほらほらほら
This way.
こっち
This drool is what came out from inside.
このよだれなのが中から出てきたやつなの
I don't understand it anymore though.
わかんなくなっちゃったけど
Every reaction is kind of cute, isn't it?
反応がいちいちちょっとかわいいですよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I don't think it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしくないと思いますね
I'm not embarrassed.
恥ずかしくない
It's embarrassing even if you can see it.
やっぱ見えても恥ずかしいですもんね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I'm putting it out by myself.
一人で出してますからね
Then I'll put it out too.
じゃあ僕も出すんで
Wouldn't it be embarrassing if I came out too?
僕も出したら恥ずかしくないんじゃないですか?
together.
一緒に
Mika-san, why don't you take off your top a little?
みかさんもちょっと上脱ぎません?
Me too?
私もですか?
Yes, just a moment.
はい、ちょっと
Above or above
上っていうか上
mosquito.
か
You took your clothes off.
脱 ぎましたね
I took it off.
脱ぎました
Why are you so beautiful?
なんでこんなにきれいなんですか?
Yeah.
うん
Why are you so beautiful?
なんでこんなにきれいなんですか?
My body.
体が
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
It's so beautiful.
すごいきれいですね
thank you.
ありがとう
No, really.
いや本当に
Ah, I need to take off my clothes a little lower in that direction.
あ、そっち方向ちょっと下は脱がないとね
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうですね
Yes.
はいって
You can put it on top.
上入れるよね
I agree.
そうですね
Isn't the top one and the bottom one missing?
上一枚下はなしですかね
yes.
はい
It's like this though.
こんな 感じですけど
こんな感じですけど
What happened?
どうしました?
I'm with you.
一緒です
Applause, I would be happy if I received applause for the first time.
拍手、初めて拍手してもらったら嬉しい
I'm with you.
一緒です
We're together.
一緒ですね
Didn't you lick me just now?
さっき僕舐めたじゃないですか?
Didn't you lick it?
舐めたじゃないですか?
Let's enjoy this together for a while,
これもちょっとみがはんに一緒に、
I'd like you to lick me with me.
一緒にっていうか舐めて欲しいんですけど
In return.
お返しに
Maybe we can do it for each other a little bit.
ちょっとやっぱお互いにやってもいいかな
I agree.
そうですね
I can hear the wind.
風なんか聞き分けがある
He said it was really good.
すごく良いよって
thank you.
ありがとう
Well, maybe I should just lie down like this.
ちょっとじゃあ、こう寝っ転がったりとかしたらいいのかな
yes.
はい
It's really beautiful.
マジ綺麗ですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
happy.
嬉しい
I'm so happy, such a beautiful person.
もう嬉しいです、こんな綺麗な人
It's kind of embarrassing.
なんか恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですよ
After licking it a little more, I started to feel embarrassed.
もうちょっと舐めたら恥ずかしくなってきました
We're together.
一緒ですね
Well then.
じゃあ
I don't remember anything about what we met here today.
ここで今日会ったのも何か覚えないんで
different.
違う
Excuse me.
失礼します
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
Excuse me.
失礼しますって
what?
何ですか?
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
The face.
顔が
what?
何ですか?
The face.
顔が
Her face is cute.
顔がかわいい
Do you know that the tip feels good?
先っぽ気持ちいいって知ってるんですか?
Well, I don't know.
え、知らないです
Well then, you're a genius.
じゃあ、天才ですね
I don't know.
知らないです
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
I'm not embarrassed.
恥 ずかしくないです
It feels a little too good.
ちょっと気持ち良すぎます
Where did you get this kind of training?
どこでこんな鍛えできたんですか?
I don't know.
わかんないですよ
Oh, there's yozare.
あ、ヨザレが
You know that tip feels good, right?
先っぽ気持ちいいって知ってるじゃないですか?
Well, I don't know.
え、知らないですよ
It feels good.
気持ちいいんですよ
I've already said it.
もう言っちゃいますけど
A little cute.
ちょっとかわいい
I don't know.
知らないね
i don't know.
知らない
Please understand the basics.
いっかぎをわかってください
It feels really good.
本当に気持ちいいんですよ
what?
何ですか?
What I'm licking is from the beginning.
舐めてるもの、最初より
It's getting really big.
すごい大きくなってます
I'll just lick the tip.
先っぽばっか舐めるから
What, no?
え、ダメですか?
It's not a bad thing though.
ダメじゃないんですけど
It's not bad at all though.
全くダメじゃないんですけど
I'm just talking about the tip.
って言ってんの、先っぽだけ
Wait, no.
ちょっと、ダメですよ
i don't know.
知らない
The feeling of being teased is terrible.
じらされてる感じがやばいです
is that so?
そうですか?
Please tease me.
じらしてください
I'm not teasing you.
じらしてないんですよ
Well then, please do it like this.
じゃ、がっつりこうやってください
I'm annoyed enough, already.
十分じらされてるんですけど、もう
Well, a little.
まあ、ちょっと
Hey, let's do it.
ちょっと、やりまして
Is it in the back?
奥ですか?
Because it's big.
大きいから
One more time.
もう一回
Is it one more time?
もう一回ですか?
Isn't it annoying?
うってならないですか?
Was it okay?
大丈夫でした?
But it's big, so I'm a little disappointed.
でも、大きいから、ちょっとうって
Isn't it annoying?
うってならないですか?
So, is it a little difficult to reach the back of your mouth?
じゃあ、口は奥までがちょっとしんどいですか?
How about panko?
パンコはどうですか?
To the back.
奥まで
Well, it's okay.
まあ、大丈夫です
It's okay though.
大丈夫なんですけど
Well then, there you go.
じゃあ、そっちで
Over there.
そっちで
There.
そ っちで
It's a little deep inside.
ちょっと、あんま奥だと
It's painful, isn't it?
苦しいですよね
Now, please lie down for a while.
じゃあ、ちょっと寝っ転がってください
This sound.
この音が
I hear a sound.
音がします
yes.
はい
It's making a lot of noise.
すごい鳴ってるんですよ、音が
I can hear it if I'm quiet.
静かにすると聞こえますけど
Just touch me.
ちょっと、触って
what?
何ですか?
big.
大きい
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
After adding a little bit of this, it will get even bigger.
これ、ちょっと入れた後、さらに大きくなる
Do you understand?
分かります?
I understand.
分かります
It's tough.
きついですね
Is it tight?
きついですか?
It's tight and feels good.
きつくて気持ちいいです
It's a little too scratchy.
ちょっと、こすれすぎますね
It feels really good though.
めっちゃ気持ちいいですけど
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
It feels so good
めっちゃ気持ちいい
is.
です
It feels really good.
め っちゃ気持ちいいです
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
Show me your cheeks.
ほっぺを見せて
Take it off yourself.
自分でさ、外して
Ah, I saw it.
あ、見えちゃった
I could see it.
見えちゃいましたね
After all, you don't even hide your face.
やっぱり顔も隠さないでしょ
It's standing even better than this one.
こっちよりもせっかく立ってる
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいですかね
Eh, but this one is standing.
え、でも立ってますよね、これ
It's just my imagination.
気のせいです
I'm standing here too.
こっちも立ってるよ
This one is standing too.
こ っちも立ってるよ
It's just my imagination.
気のせいです
Can you all move up a little bit?
みんなちょっと上で動いてもらったりできます?
It's okay.
いいんですよ
He will listen to anything.
なんでも聞いてくれるです
In the meantime, it's a little scary.
またの間に、ちょっとやば
Your body is really beautiful.
体ほんときれいですよね
What's a lot?
何がたくさんよ
Seriously.
まじで
Just looking at her body makes me cringe.
体見てるだけでちょっとじんこ立っちゃう
ERROR
すみません、あんま言わないほうがいいか
No, I'm happy.
いや、うれしいです
Is it true?
ほんとですか?
It's very erotic.
めっちゃエロいですね
I'm happy.
うれしいんだ
Well, I'm happy.
え、うれしいんですよ
It's erotic, seriously.
エロいっす、まじで
Tele, tele.
テレ、テレちゃう
Is it true?
ほんとですか?
yes.
はい
I thought they were laughing at me because I was lying down in front of them.
前らで寝転がってるの笑われてるのかと思った
Well, that's not true.
え、違いますね
Well, it's Mae et al.
まあ、前らですもんね
I'm with you.
一緒です
That's right.
ですよね
ERROR
ちょ、かわいい
Please come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち来てください
The face.
顔が
What is it?
なんすか?
Let's do it.
めっちゃこう
Oh, it hit my boobs.
あ、おっぱい当たった
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Oh, not at all.
あ、全然
Please guess at all.
全然当ててくださいって
a,
あ、
Hey, your face looks terrible.
ちょ、 顔がやばい
Hey, that's cute.
ちょ、かわいいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I just snorted.
鼻息が今かかりました
Can I take a guess?
ちょっと当てていいんですか?
this.
これ
Ah, that's a bit spot on.
あ、ちょっと当たっちゃってる
Ah, that's a little scary.
あ、 ちょっとやばい
The place is.
場 所が
The location.
場所が
just.
ちょうど
ERROR
いい場所
Just the skin.
ちょうど肌
Is it a coincidence?
たまたまっすか?
this.
これ
Maybe just the location.
たぶんちょうど場所が
Ah, I'll wait a moment.
あ、ちょっと待ってます
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
Hey, hey.
ねえ、ちょっと
It's rubbing off, isn't it?
こすっちゃってるじゃないですか
ERROR
こするでしょ
This is it if you have it.
あったらこれ
Hey, why is it that color?
ねえ、なんでそんな色いんすか?
I'm not aware of it at all.
全然自覚ないんですけど
That's not the best thing.
それが一番良くないですね
Look, there's a little dick.
ほら、ちょっとチンコが
I'm counting on this too.
これも当てにいってますよね
You're counting on it.
当てにいってますよね
It just happened.
たまたまです
by chance.
たまたま
Is it a coincidence?
たまたまっすか?
It just happened.
たまたまです
just.
ちょうど
Just.
ちょうどです
The location.
位置が
ERROR
位置がいい位置
just.
ちょうど
Can you please straddle me once?
ちょっと、こう、一回またがったりとかしてもらっていいですか?
Are you going to straddle it?
またがるんですか?
yes.
はい
amazing.
すごい
What is it?
なんすか?
Straddle it, because it's a little closed,
またがって、だってちょっと閉まって、
this.
これ
Will it close?
閉まる?
oh yeah.
そうそう
ERROR
収納して
Can I have you store it?
収納してもらっていいですか?
It's closed.
閉まりました
Thank you for closing.
閉まってもらってありがとうございます
amazing.
すごい
What's going on?
どうなってるんですか?
Oku, don't you like it so much?
奥、あんま好きじゃないですか?
I like it.
好きです
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
Ok, let's guess.
奥、当てましょうよ
I guess.
当 てます
amazing.
すごい
Are you putting it in the back now?
今、奥に当ててるんですか?
I'll guess.
当てます
May I help you a little?
ちょっと手伝いましょうか?
I hit it really deep.
めちゃくちゃ奥に当てます
amazing.
すごい
Really hard.
めっちゃ、ガンガン
Gang Gang.
ガ ン ガ ン
Mikan, your butt is round, but it's really nice.
みかん、お尻はまん丸ですけど、めっちゃいいっすね
Oh, really?
え、本当ですか?
That's a nice butt.
いいお尻ですよね
I'm so happy.
めっちゃうれしい
Oh, it's kind of nice.
え、なんか、いいっすね
ERROR
まじでエロいっすね、なんか下半身も
Isn't your whole body erotic?
全身エロくないっすか?
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
It's totally okay.
全然大丈夫
Is everything okay?
全然大丈夫?
It's really, really painful.
めっちゃ、めっちゃ痛いっすね
Are you starting to cry?
泣くだし?
good.
いい
I started crying.
泣くだしよって
Are you starting to cry?
泣くだしよ?
nice.
いいね
That's fine.
いいですよ
It's really hard.
め っちゃ、 ガ ン ガ ン
I said okay, then I said okay.
いいよって言ってから、いいよって言ったから、
I released it, was it good?
出したんですけど、よかったんですか?
It was good.
よかったです
Well then, good for you.
じゃあ、よかったです
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
気持ちよかったです
I had no idea he was such an erotic person.
こんなエロい人だと、思わなかったです
Do you usually hide it?
隠してるんですか、普段は?
what?
何ですか?
Are you hiding it?
隠してるんですか?
Hidden... it felt good.
隠...気持ちよかった
There are times when I don't hide it.
隠しないときもあるんですが
Seriously.
マジで
I guess it's okay if I wash it a little.
一応これちょっと、洗えば大丈夫かな
Let's wash it properly.
洗いましょう、ちゃんと
yes.
はい